githyp.com 2019-08-15

# Privacy Policy – GitHyp

Last modified on **May 24, 2018**

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains HypTrain Technology, LLC’s (“HypTrain Technology’s”) information-gathering and dissemination practices for GitHyp’s website, www.GitHyp.com (the “Site”). GitHyp provides the gaming community and industry with current statistics and historical data.

GitHyp takes your privacy rights seriously and has posted this Privacy Policy to let GitHyp users know what information GitHyp collects from you, why GitHyp collects it and what GitHyp does with it. GitHyp’s goal is to collect and use only that information that GitHyp thinks is necessary for GitHyp’s legitimate business interests, such as to better understand and serve you, the GitHyp community, to provide better service and to improve marketing of GitHyp.

**Acceptance of These Terms**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the GitHyp Terms of Service of the Site. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service of the Site, please do not provide GitHyp with any information and do not use the GitHyp Site or other services. Your continued use of the GitHyp Site after the Privacy Policy has been modified will signify your acceptance of the changes for information gathered after the date of the change.

**Does this Privacy Policy apply to you?**

This privacy policy covers GitHyp’s information collection and use practices for anyone who uses the Site. Except as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy, GitHyp will not share your personally identifiable information with any third parties unless you give GitHyp permission to do so or except as required by law or to cooperate with law enforcement authorities.

This Site, however, contains links to other websites, advertisers and other third parties. By clicking on any of these links, you are leaving the Site. GitHyp has no control over the information collected from or about you by any third-party after you have left the Site. _This Privacy Policy does not cover the data collection and use practices of any third-party linked to GitHyp._ GitHyp assumes no liability and is not responsible for any practices of such third-party web sites, including their privacy practices or content.

**What information, including personally identifiable information, does GitHyp collect from and about you?**

Our goal in collecting information from and about you is to provide you with the best web experience possible. In order to provide you with our services, GitHyp collects two types of information from its community: passive technical information; and information you voluntarily provide to GitHyp, including personally identifiable information. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, GitHyp is the Data Controller of your Personal Data who will determine the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed.

Passive Technical Information. GitHyp automatically collects certain technical information for each visitor, including your IP address, the type of browser you use to surf the Internet, your screen resolution, and your computer’s operating system. Your IP address tells GitHyp both your Internet Service Provider (ISP) and the general geographic location from which you are connecting. GitHyp may also use your IP address to track the date and time you accessed the Site, how long you stayed on the Site and what pages you visited. This information is used internally by GitHyp to help provide a good web experience to our community, including proper formatting for our web pages.

This information is obtained using third-party Service Providers. Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

This information is also provided in the aggregate to third parties, including potential business partners and advertisers, to describe basic use patterns for the Site, but this information is not linked to any personally identifiable information before it is disclosed unless GitHyp has obtained your consent.

In addition, GitHyp uses cookies on this Site. Cookies are small data text files that are sent from a server computer to your computer during a browsing session so that the web site may track your activities on the web site. Cookies are typically stored on your computer’s hard drive and are used by web sites to simulate a continuous connection to that site. Cookies, by themselves, do not necessarily let a web site know any personally identifying information about you, such as your real name, address, etc., unless you previously provided that information at the web site or have set your preferences in your browser to provide that information. However, any personal information you use to registered for an account will use cookies to save your information and password so that you don’t have to reenter it each time you visit the Site.

**What other organizations besides GitHyp may be collecting information from you on the Site?**

GitHyp may use outside advertising companies to display banner advertisements on the Site. Banner advertisements may also contain cookies, and appear to be coming from GitHyp; but, in reality, they are coming from third parties who are serving advertisements on the Site. GitHyp has no control over the privacy practices of any third-party, and the manner in which any third-party uses your information is not protected by the terms of this Privacy Policy. Further, once you leave the Site, GitHyp does not control the privacy policies or the privacy practices of any third parties.

**What happens to my information after GitHyp collects it?**

When GitHyp collects information from you, GitHyp does not share any information with third parties outside of GitHyp without your consent. You will give this consent by “opting-in” to having your information shared with third parties when you register. These third parties may include GitHyp’s marketing partners, who may want specific information to better shape their marketing efforts. Additionally, GitHyp provides the community the opportunity to be sent newsletters and information about promotional events, publications, and marketing events. Again, GitHyp will not send this information to you unless you “opt in” for these services and publications.

In addition, GitHyp will not sell, dispose, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent except as specifically set forth in this paragraph and in the preceding paragraph. When you choose to supply GitHyp with your personally identifying information, GitHyp compiles this information in a database with other GitHyp community members’ information and GitHyp reserves the right to transfer this information to a successor, related entity or to a third-party purchasing or succeeding to GitHyp’s assets.

**How long is this information retained?**

GitHyp will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

GitHyp will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

**How can you review and correct information you submitted to the Site, unsubscribe, or opt out?**

Your saved Account, Privacy Settings, and Personal Details can be viewed, updated, or deleted at any time by visiting https://www.githyp.com/account.

To unsubscribe from our mailing lists and remove your information from our databases, you can send an email to info@githyp.com. In this email, you must include your user name and password, and a description of the information you would like to change.

Additionally, if you choose to receive GitHyp newsletters, you may unsubscribe from this service in the manner indicated in each newsletter.

**What kinds of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under GitHyp’s control?**

GitHyp uses industry standard security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under GitHyp’s control, including firewalls and other security measures. Nonetheless, due to the inherent dangers of the Internet, GitHyp cannot guarantee the protection of such information against loss, misuse, or alteration.

**A special notice to parents of children under the age of 13.**

The Site is a general audience web site and is intended to be used by adults and teens (13+) interested in the world of movies and video games. It is not intended for children under the age of 13 and GitHyp will not collect any personal identifiable information for such children. ** **

**Modifications to this privacy policy.**

GitHyp reserves the right, at GitHyp’s discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time to comply with any applicable state or federal regulations, to utilize new technologies or to improve your GitHyp experience, so please check back periodically to review our Privacy Policy. If GitHyp changes any portion of this Privacy Policy, the change will be posted in this document so that you will always know what information GitHyp gathers, how GitHyp might use that information, and to whom GitHyp will disclose such information. GitHyp will not change the use and dissemination practices related to information obtained under a prior version of this Privacy Policy without your prior consent. This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 24, 2018.
